Guide to the Computational Engineering Building (Duncan Hall) Construction records, 1981-2002 UA 366
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Project Manager Files (Alphabetical)
  - Subseries H:
    - HACKO Drawings
      - Sheet PC-113.1, 7/31/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 68)
      - Sheet PC-114, 4/2/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 69)
      - Sheet PC-115, 8/24/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 70)
      - Sheet PC-116, 4/21/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 71)
      - Sheet PC-117, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 72)
      - Sheet PC-118, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 73)
      - Sheet PC-119, 4/21/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 74)
      - Sheet PC-120, 4/21/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 75)
      - Sheet PC-121, 4/21/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 76)
      - Sheet PC-122, 11/30/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 77)
      - Sheet PC-130, 8/11/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 78)
      - Sheet PC-131, 8/11/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 79)
      - Sheet PC-132, 8/11/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 80)
      - Sheet PC-133, 8/11/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 81)
      - Sheet PC-134, 9/13/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 82)
      - Sheet PC-135, 9/15/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 83)
      - Sheet PC-136, 9/15/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 84)
      - Sheet PC-137, 9/15/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 85)
      - Sheet PC-138, 9/15/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 86)
      - Sheet PC-139, 9/15/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 87)
      - Sheet PC-140, 9/28/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 88)
      - Sheet PC-141, 9/15/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 89)
      - Sheet PC-142, 9/28/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 90)
      - Sheet PC-143, 9/15/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 91)
      - Sheet PC-201, 4/21/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 92)
      - Sheet PC-202, 4/21/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 93)
      - Sheet PC-203, 6/5/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 94)
      - Sheet PC-204, 5/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 95)
      - Sheet PC-205, 11/28/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 96)
      - Sheet PC-206, 12/5/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 97)
      - Sheet PC-207, 4/21/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 98)
      - Sheet PC-208, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 99)
      - Sheet PC-209, 9/13/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 100)
      - Sheet PC-210, 4/21/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 101)
      - Sheet PC-210, 9/13/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 102)
      - Sheet PC-211, 11/30/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 103)
      - Sheet PC-212, 7/24/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 104)
      - Sheet PC-213, 11/19/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 105)
      - Sheet PC-214, 11/27/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 106)
      - Sheet PC-215, 12/6/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 107)
      - Sheet PC-301, 5/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 108)
      - Sheet PC-302, 6/6/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 109)
      - Sheet PC-303, 4/27/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 110)
      - Sheet PC-307, 4/21/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 111)
      - Sheet PC-308, 5/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 112)
      - Sheet PC-309, 4/21/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 113)
      - Sheet PC-310, 5/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 114)
      - Sheet PC-311, 5/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 115)
      - Sheet PC-312, 6/7/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 116)
      - Sheet PC-313, 5/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 117)
      - Sheet PC-314, 4/2/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 118)
      - Sheet PC-315, 5/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 119)
      - Sheet PC-315.1, 9/25/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 120)
      - Sheet PC-317, 8/24/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 121)
      - Sheet PC-318, 6/7/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 122)
      - Sheet PC-319, 6/7/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 123)
      - Sheet PC-320, 6/20/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 124)
      - Sheet PC-321, 6/20/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 125)
      - Sheet PC-322, 6/20/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 126)
      - Sheet PC-323, 6/20/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 127)
      - Sheet PC-324, 6/20/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 128)
      - Sheet PC-324, 9/7/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 129)
      - Sheet PC-326, 9/7/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 130)
      - Sheet PC-328, 9/25/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 131)
      - Sheet PC-329, 7/24/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 132)
      - Sheet PC-327, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 133)
      - Sheet PC-330, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 134)
      - Sheet PC-330.1-.4, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 135-138)
      - Sheet PC-333.1-.5, 9/29/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 139-144)
      - Sheet PC-334, 10/17/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 145)
      - Sheet PC-335, 10/17/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 146)
      - Sheet PC-336, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 147)
      - Sheet PC-337, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 148)
      - Sheet PC-338, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 149)
      - Sheet PC-339, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 150)
      - Sheet PC-340, 10/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 151)
      - Sheet PC-341, 11/2/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 152)
      - Sheet PC-344, 11/27/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 153)
      - Sheet PC-345, 10/24/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 154)
      - Sheet PC-345.1, 10/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 155)
      - Sheet PC-346, 10/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 156)
      - Sheet PC-346.1, 10/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 157)
      - Sheet PC-355, 11/27/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 158)
      - Sheet PC-355.1-.4, 10/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 159-162)
      - Sheet PC-356, 11/28/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 163)
      - Sheet PC-356.1, 10/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 164)
      - Sheet PC-360, 10/18/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 165)
      - Sheet PC-361, 11/9/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 166)
      - Sheet PC-361.1, 11/9/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 167)
      - Sheet PC-363, 11/20/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 168)
      - Sheet PC-364, 10/26/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 169)
      - Sheet PC-365, 11/30/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 170)
      - Sheet PC-366, 11/30/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 171)
      - Sheet PC-366.1, 11/30/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 172)
      - Sheet PC-368, 11/27/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 173)
      - Sheet PC-375, 11/28/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 174)
      - Sheet PC-401, 6/6/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 175)
      - Sheet PC-402, 6/6/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 176)
      - Sheet PC-403, 6/6/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 177)
      - Sheet PC-404, 5/25/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 178)
      - Sheet PC-405, 4/19/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 179)
      - Sheet PC-406, 4/19/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 180)
      - Sheet PC-407, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 181)
      - Sheet PC-408, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 182)
      - Sheet PC-409, 9/7/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 183)
      - Sheet PC-410, 7/24/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 184)
      - Sheet PC-411, 10/16/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 185)
      - Sheet PC-412, 11/9/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 186)
      - Sheet PC-413, 11/9/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 187)
      - Sheet PC-414, 11/28/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 188)
      - Sheet Damaged, n.d. (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 189)
      - Sheet Damaged, n.d. (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 190)
    - Hardrock Erectors, Inc., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - HAKCO Progress Photos
    - Hardrock Erectors, Inc., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Hartman Building (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Houston Builders Hardware, Inc., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Huntingdon File #7, Maxim Tech Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Huntingdon File #6, Maxim Tech Reports, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Huntingdon File #5, Maxim Tech Reports, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Huntingdon File #4, Maxim Tech Reports, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Huntingdon File #3, Maxim Tech Reports, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Huntingdon File #2, Maxim Tech Reports, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Huntingdon File #1, Maxim Tech Reports, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Huntingdon File Extras to Contrat, 6/1995 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Subseries I:
    - International Precast and Steel Erectors, Inc., 12/1995 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - International Precast and Steel Erectors, Inc., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Subseries J:
    - A.L. Jenson, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Subseries K:
    - Kendall/ Heaton Associates, Inc. #3, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Kendall/ Heaton Associates, Inc. #2, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Kendall/ Heaton Associates, Inc. #1, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Kendall/ Heaton Associates, Inc. Re: PCC #88, RFI #348, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Kendall/ Heaton Associates, Inc. Submittal No. 10205-01E, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Kendall/ Heaton Associates, Inc. Sketches, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Kenmor File #7, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Kenmor File #6, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Kenmor File #5, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Kenmor File #4, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Kenmor File #3, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Kenmor File #2, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Kenmor File Extra Work, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Kirby Simmons (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Subseries L:
    - Laboratory Specialists, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Landris and Gyr Powers, Inc., 1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - W.L. Lashley and Associates, Inc., Louvers, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - W.L. Lashley and Associates, Inc., Access Doors, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - W.L. Lashley and Associates, Inc., Fire Exit, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Laticrete International, 10/1996 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Waiver of Liens, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Lissiak Engineers, Inc., Re-shoring for Pan Joist Construction, 10/4/1991 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Re-shoring for Pan Joist Construcion, 10/4/1991 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 8-9)
  - Subseries M:
    - Marek Brothers System, Inc. #3, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Marek Brothers System, Inc. #2, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Marek Brothers System, Inc. #1, 1955-1996 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Marek Brothers System, Inc., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Marek Brothers System, Inc., Extras, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Mats, Inc., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - MCI Services, 1/1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - MLN Company, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - MLN Co. Extra, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Monoprinted Tile Memo, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Mike Montgomery, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Walter P. Moore and Association, Inc. File, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Prairie Restoration Project, "As Built" C2.6, Rice University Road Improvements, Striping, 7/23/1993 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 10)
  - Subseries N:
    - Otto Nachlas, 11/1995 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - I.A. Naman and Associates, 11/1996 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Charlie Nelson, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Subseries O:
    - Offenhauser Company, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Offenhauser Co. Approved Shop Drawings, 9/18/1996 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - Ribbed Aluminum Soffit Closer, A5.16, 9/4/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 11)
      - Details of Closer @ S.W. Scupper, 2-S (5 Pages), 6/20/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 12-16)
      - Aluminum Monitor Covers, 1, 9/3/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 17)
      - S/O NO. 5856, E7, Sheets 1 to 4 of 4, 9/20/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 18-21)
    - OSHA Fall Standards, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - John Outram and Associates, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Subseries P:
    - Pearland Industries, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Pecco Cranes, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Permits, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Pier Information, 8/1995 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Pioneer Concrete of Texas, Inc., 1995 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Plaster Glas, Inc., 3/16/1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Power Shutdown Meeting, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Praire Restoration Project, As Built (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Prestige Interior Corp., 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Progress Photos (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Project Correspondence, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project Correspondence, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - KHA Partial Punch Lists, 9-10/1996 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - KHA Partial Punch Lists, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Punch List Schedule, 8/1996 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Above Ceiling Closeup Punchlists, One Line to Thirteen Line, 6-7/1996 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Subseries R:
    - RAM Mechanical, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Regional Construction Resources #6, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Regional Construction Resources #5, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Regional Construction Resources #4, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Regional Construction Resources #3, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Regional Construction Resources #2, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Regional Construction Resources #1, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Regional Construction Drawings: Structural Roof Drawings
      - S/O 268, Sheet D1, 7/31/1995 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 1)
      - S/O 268, Sheet W1-W6, 6/1995-9/1995 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 2-7)
      - S/O 268M, Sheet 8-21, 1/29/1996 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 88-100)
      - S/O 268, Sheet 1-82, 6/1995-10/1995 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 8-87)
    - Kelly Rhoades, 7/1995 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Rice University Correspondence #1, 12/1994-9/1995 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Rice University Correspondence #2, 3/1995-3/1995 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Rice University Correspondence #3, 11/1995-3/1996 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Rice University Correspondence #4, 4/1996-11/1996 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Rice University Correspondence #5, 6/1996-11/1996 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Ryder Co., Inc., 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Subseries S:
    - Security, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Sheplers, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Sheplers, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Sidewalk Changes, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Sikes Drapery Corp., 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - SITE: Court Yard Sidewalk- Annotated Plans, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Floyd, Smith and Rios, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Sneads, Inc., 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Southeast Fire Protection, Inc., Invoices, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Southeast Fire Protection, Inc., 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Spec 10 Sale, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Steel Kicker @ Precast Hanger, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Sterling Janitorial Service Agreement, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Stewart Filmscreen Corp., 11/1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Structural Inspection, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Suncoast Postension Corp., 1995 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Switch, Data, and Power Relocation at Deans Office, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Symphony Concrete, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Subseries T:
    - Te-Ko Contractors, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Terrazzo Floor, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File #5, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File #4, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File #3, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File #2, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File #1, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File, Drilled Shafts, 1/18/1995-2/27/1995 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File, Basement, CE Building, 4/4/1995-5/11/1995 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File, Ground Floor, 6/7/1995-7/11/1995; 3/13/1996 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - Ground Floor, Grade Beam- Pour #1, S1-S2, P1, 4/4/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 22)
      - Ground Floor, Grade Beam- Pour #2, S4-S25, P6, 5/2/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 23)
      - Ground Floor, Grade Beam- Pour #3, S7-S8, P7, 7/13/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 24)
      - Ground Floor, Grade Beam Slab, S10, P8, 6/7/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 25)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File, 2nd Floor, 6/8/1995-10/9/1995 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - Second Floor 1-8, S/11-S/12, P9, 8/7/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 26)
      - COLS SUPT Lvl 2, COLS, P10, 7/27/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 27)
      - COLS SUPT Lvl 2, 1 to 8, S14, P10, 6/8/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 28)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File, 2nd Floor, 10/11/1995 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File, 3rd Foor, 8/22/1995-9/8/1995 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Third Floor: 1-8, S15/S16, P11, 5/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 29)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File, 3rd Foor, 9/8/1995-10/24/1995 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File, 3rd Foor, 11/3/1995-11/10/1995 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File, 4rd Foor, 9/11/1995-10/11/1995 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - Fourth Floor, 1 to 8, S19-S20, P13, 5/18/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 30)
      - COLS SUPT Lvl, COLS, P18, 7/27/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 31)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File, 4th Floor, 10/11/1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Texas Cold Finished Steel File, Lecture Hall #1, #2, LH-1, 4/5/1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Tower Crane- Inspection Reports #4718 PC-2000 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - TREMCO, Inc., 1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - TTSS Corp. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Subseries V:
    - Valentine Steel Services, Inc., 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Vaulted Ceiling and Custom Artwork, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Veazey Corp., 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Subseries W
    - Wall Color, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - July Waivers (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Warranties C.D., 1995 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Warranty, 4/1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Weber-Blake Foundation Co., 1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Woodcraft Pavilion Co., 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Westbrook Construction Co., Inc., 1995 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - James Whitaker, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Working Drawings, 5/1995 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - WW Drilling Co., Inc. Daily Reports, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - WW Drilling Co., 1995 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Requests for Information
  - Request for Information Logs, 9/11/1996 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Rice Memo Directives, 3/1996 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Request for Information, 1-20, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Request for Information, 21-40, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Request for Information, 41-60, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Request for Information, 61-80, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Request for Information, 81-100, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Request for Information, 101-120, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Request for Information, 121-`140, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Request for Information, 141-160, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Request for Information, 161-180, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Request for Information, 181-200, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Request for Information, 201-220, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Request for Information, 221-240, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Request for Information, 241-260, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Request for Information, 261-280, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Request for Information, 281-300, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Request for Information, 301-320, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Request for Information, 321-340, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Request for Information, 341-360, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Request for Information, 361-380, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Request for Information, 381-400, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Request for Information, 401-420, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Request for Information, 421-440, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Request for Information, 441-447, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Field Reports, 1994-1996
  - Accident Reports, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Architect's Field Reports, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Field Reports (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Brown and Root Building Company, Monthly Status Reports, 4/1995 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Brown and Root Building Company, Monthly Status Reports, 5/1995-10/1995 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Brown and Root Building Company, Monthly Status Reports, 10/1996-12/1995 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Brown and Root Building Company, Monthly Status Reports, 1/1996-4/1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Brown and Root Building Company, Monthly Status Reports, 5/1996-7/1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Brown and Root Building Company, Monthly Status Reports, 8/1996-10/1996 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 12/1995-1/1996 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 1/1996 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 1/1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 2/1996 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 2/1996 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 2/1996-3/1996 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 3/1996-4/1996 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 4/1996 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 4/1996 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 4/1996-5/1996 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 5/1996-6/1996 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 6/1996 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 6/1996-7/1996 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 7/1996 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 7/1996-8/1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 9/1996-10/1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 10/1996-11/1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Subcontractors Daily Reports, 11/1996-12/1996 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Superintendant Daily Reports, 1/1995-7/1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Superintendant Daily Reports, 8/1995-1/1996 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Superintendant Daily Reports, 2/1996-6/1996 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Superintendant Daily Reports, 7/1996-11/1996 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Safety Meetings, 1994-1996
  - Safety Correspondence, 2/1995-10/1995 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Safety Meetings, 2/1995-10/1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Safety Meetings, 11/1995-2/1996 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Safety Meetings, 2/1996-5/1996 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Safety Meetings, 6/1996-10/1996 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Safety Topics, 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Meeting Minutes and Schedules
  - Progress Meeting Minutes, 9/1996-11/1996 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Progress Meeting Minutes, 9/1996-11/1996 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Project Manuals, 1994-1996
  - Project Manual Vol. 1, Division 1-14, 11/15/1994 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Project Manual Vol I. Division 1-14, Supplement, 1/20/1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Project Manual Vol I. Division 1-14, Supplement, 2/1/1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Project Manual Vol I. Division 1-14, Supplement, 3/1/1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Project Manual Vol I. Division 1-14, Supplement, 8/23/1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Project Manual Vol I. Division 1-14, Supplement, 2/6/1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Project Manual Vol I. Division 1-14, Supplement, 3/11/1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Project Manual Vol I. Division 1-14, Supplement, 4/19/1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Project Manual Vol I. Division 1-14, Supplement, 5/29/1996 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Project Manual Vol II. Division 15-16, 11/15/1994 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Project Manual Vol II. Division 15-16, Supplement, 2/1/1995 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Project Manual Vol II. Division 15-16, Supplement "COR 4", 4/11/1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Project Manual Vol. II Division 15-16 Supplement, 6/28/1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Project Manual Vol. II Division 15-16 Supplement, 9/28/1995 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Project Manual Vol. II Division 15-16 Supplement, 10/31/1995 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Project Manual Vol. II Division 15-16 Supplement, 11/17/1995 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Project Manual Vol. II Division 15-16 Supplement, 3/11/1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Project Notebooks, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Drawings